[Music]
201 and
support forent be awesome Amica I can't
I can't listen to this maldi janetti
kills meat in his attic is there
anything to do in Boston that doesn't
have to do with eating uh no how do you
like them
pineapples but you know what we should
totally go apple picking while we're
there we're not going apple picking this
isn't a date we're going apple picking
we're not going apple picking take the
ice bucket challenge right that started
off really good ALS brought all this
money in it started off with all these
great people right then all of a sudden
these C and D list celebrities start
going wait a minute I should get in on
that thing and the next thing I'm
watching Carrot Top do the Ice Bucket
Challenge and I rather like if he dumped
like a bucket of Hamas on his head or
scorpion I'd be like I will send more
money
now hey America Larry Wilmore here if
you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me